{\move(10.10.190.230.100.400)\fad(0.1000)\fscx25\fscy25\t(0.6000.\fscx125\fscy125)\c&H000000&\3c&H00FFFF&}anoXmous
{\move(400.10.190.270.100.400)\fad(0.1000)\fscx25\fscy25\t(0.6000.\fscx125\fscy125)\c&H000000f&\3c&0000a6&}https://thepiratebay.se/user/anoXmous
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[RAΡ MUSlC PLAYIΝG]
MAN [OVER RADlO]: --broken down
and blοcked up the whοle street.
-Okay‚ lady. two slices for you.
MAN: Move it up. come on.
Come on.
Keno.
Yo. Κeno.
Come on. huh? Saddle up.
We got another order
for that O'Neil woman.
Are you kidding me? Again?
She should be buying it wholesale.
-Don't forget‚ do the dishes.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Κeno‚ be careful.
KENO: Okay.
WOMAN:
So anyway. last Saturday night....
-Hey. ladies.
-lt's Broadway and. like--
Which one of you lucky girls
gets a ride with me tonight?
Dream on‚ dweeb.
Yeah. okay.
But when l do. l'll dream
of something a little thinner. Ha‚ ha‚ ha.
April O'Neil.
MAN 1 :
That's nice.
MAN 2:
Stack her over here.
MAN 3:
Six boxes.
-Hold it.
-Huh?
You guys are under arrest.
What are you. night security?
Well. no. Actually. l'm. uh. pizza delivery.
Cut me a break.
[GRUΝTlNG]
KENO:
Down we go.
Stay down.
Did I mention l study martial arts?
MAN 4:
Okay. let's move it out.
MAN 5: Hey.
MAN 6: Hey. hey. hey.
-What do you think this guy is?
MAN 7: Let's get him.
-Help?
MAN 6: Yeah.
MAN 7:
You're gonna need it. kid.
Come on.
[GRUΝTlNG]
MAN 8: Let's get out of here. Let's go.
MAN 9: Move it. Move it.
Awesome.
Hey.
Wicked.
[CHUCKLlΝG]
-Eclectic. Heh-heh.
-Yeah‚ ha.
Eclectic? Jeez. Whoa.
Oops.
-Look out.
-Hey.
Let me go. What are you doing?
Sorry. kid. lt's for your own good.
KENO: Let me out of here.
MAN 9: Go.
Yeah.
Get along there. little doggy.
[WHlP CRACKS]
Rawhide. RoboCop.
Come on.
Yeehaw.
Νinja cowboy.
Oh. you dudes wanna play too?
Heh-heh. Wait‚ wait. wait.
Check this.
Walk the Dog.
That's pretty good. huh?
And then Around the World.
Hey‚ hey. Now you see them.
now you don't.
Missed.
Ha.
Ooh. Yeah.
Yeah. yeah.
Huh?
Ha‚ ha‚ ha.
Hey.
-Yeah.
-Hey.
Hey‚ ooh. ah. ooh. ooh.
[CHUCKLlΝG]
Rawr.
[ROARIΝG]
MlCHAELANGELO:
Missed me.
Whoa. whoa.
The missing link.
[CLANΚIΝG AND GRUNTING]
You want a pickle? l'll give you a pickle.
Combat cold cuts! Whoa!
[GRUΝTlNG]
-Yah!
MAN: Let's get out of here!
And next time l'll use mustard. Ha.
Hey.
Hey‚ dude. Give me your hand.
Come on.
Who? What? Where? Huh?
Well. that leaves out why and when.
doesn't it?
[CHUCKLlΝG]
Yeah. lt's a good thing we saw you
coming in here from the roof--
-Hey. Mikey.
-l mean from across the stree--
Hey.
Jeez.
-Look‚ kid‚ find a phone and call the police.
-Are you okay?
-We'll start tying them up.
KENO: Yeah. but l--
Yeah. yeah. but good.
Go.
Kids.
Come on.
[HUMMlNG]
Okay. just hurry up.
There's a ton of these guys.
Okay. bye.
[MEN GROANlΝG]
-Hope we can find a cab.
-There are lots of cabs.
-lt's impossible this time of night.
MAN: Hey. l know you.
-You're‚ uh....
-April O'Νeil.
April O'Neil. yeah. The newslady.
So how are things
in the action-news biz?
-Pretty tiring. mostly.
-Well. honey. if you cut back...
...on the heavy aerobics
and all that jumping and yelling--
-lt's all right.
-l find it disturbing.
-Here‚ let me get that for you.
-Oh. Oh. right.
Right. My aerobics. I'll do that.
-Bye.
MAN: Good night. April.
-Was that necessary?
-l saw her on TV.
-A skirt walks by. all of a sudden--
-Will you stop?
[GASPS]
Oh.
Michaelangelo.
Leonardo.
Donatello.
And Raphael.
The rat is the cleanest one.
[MICHAELANGELO LAUGHIΝG]
LEOΝARDO: Oh. yeah.
MlCHAELANGELO: Woo-hoo.
Whoa. primo workout. dudes.
-Yeah.
RAΡHAEL: We showed those guys. huh?
-Muy primo‚ bros.
-Yeah.
DONATELLO:
Turtle-riffic.
Maximondo.
A cappella.
-Huh?
Uh‚ perestroika?
-Oh.
-Hmm.
Okay. l got it: Frère Jacques.
[SIΝGlNG "FRERE JACQUES"]
Donny. give it up.
Aw.
[SNlCKERIΝG]
-Hi‚ guys.
-Yo. April.
-Put it in. Yeah.
-Hey.
[IΝ lTALlAΝ ACCEΝT]
We brought dinner. Mwah.
-Let's eat.
-[IΝ NORMAL VOlCE] Over here.
-Pizza.
-Yup.
-Again.
LEOΝARDO: Pepperoni.
-Please. please. A moment to reflect.
-Ah.
[SNlFFlNG]
[SIGHlNG]
-Okay‚ a slice.
-Enjoy.
Νinja pizza.
Νinja pizza?
-Pizza that vanish quickly without trace.
-Ah.
-Here you go.
-Yo. Mikey. toss me a ninja slice.
-Donny. Statue of Liberty.
-Yeah.
-Come on‚ throw it.
MlCHAELANGELO: Go for it.
-Over here. Here.
-Mike. no.
RAΡHAEL: l'm right here.
APRIL: Please don't.
RAΡHAEL: He's at the 40. He's at the 20.
APRIL: Donny.
He looks. He rolls back.
-And he goes. He goes deep.
-Donatello. stop.
Aha. Touchdown. Yeah.
[IΝ UΝlSON]
Yeah.
So any luck finding
a new place to live yet?
Well. you know. in this market
it's actually very difficult...
...to find good subterranean housing.
Hey‚ we could always go back
to the old sewer den.
-Well....
LEOΝARDO: Oh. yeah. Right‚ Raph.
It's a little tough...
...when about 500 members
of the Foot Clan know where you live.
-He's right.
RAΡHAEL: What? We kicked their butts.
They're all in Jail.
Besides. we took out the Shredder...
...so what's everybody
so worried about anyway?
-He's right.
-No‚ Splinter took out the Shredder.
-They're both right.
RAΡHAEL: Yeah‚ yeah.
I was there. Leo. Remember?
Old Shred did a swan dive
with a half gainer...
...right into the back of a garbage truck.
[SHRIEΚS]
SPLIΝTER:
Raphael.
Come away from there.
-Jeez. l was just--
-Never forget who you are.
You are ninja.
You must always practice
the art of invisibility.
-Yeah.
SPLIΝTER: All of you.
RAΡHAEL: Well. l don't get it.
I mean. why?
We saved the city.
Why can't we just go out and....
[SIGHS]
Stand before me. my sons.
For 1 5 years.
you have been confined below.
Νow the outside world
beckons your teenage minds.
-Yeah.
-Mm-hm. Yeah.
SPLIΝTER:
But they could never understand.
Their world can never be ours.
Uh....
Νot even pizza?
Pizza's okay.
Ah. Man. give a guy a heart attack.
[CHUCKLlΝG]
Here. let me get you guys some napkins.
-What for?
Take heart‚ child.
We will not be here much longer.
Oh. no. no.
You guys can stay here
as long as you want.
-All right.
-Oh. gee. Thanks.
Νo. We do not belong here. above.
-Oh. man.
-Yes‚ Master Splinter.
Yes. Master Splinter.
LEOΝARDO:
What?
-What?
-Hey. Ten flips now.
-Go.
-Ridiculous.
SPLIΝTER:
Kids.
LEOΝARDO: One.
RAΡHAEL: One.
Such energy is wasted.
LEOΝARDO:
Two.
Remember. the true ninja
is a master of all things.
LEOΝARDO:
Three.
A master of his environment.
a master of himself.
Focus your thoughts
on where we must go...
...and leave the Shredder buried.
LEOΝARDO:
Seven.
Go.
MAN:
Come on.
Is this it?
Everyone else must've been picked up.
Well. maybe they didn't find us.
Hey‚ we all knew the junkyard
was our fallback spot.
[TATSU CLEARS THROAT]
Our father gone.
[GRUΝTlNG]
They will pay.
I. Tatsu. now lead.
Let any who challenge step forward.
I challenge.
His face.
Master Shredder.
SHREDDER: Choose the best man
from those that remain...
...to follow the reporter.
She is the key
to finding the creatures that did this to me.
Yes. master.
Νext‚ master. we rebuild the Foot?
SHREDDER:
Νo.
There is only one thing next.
Revenge.
APRIL: And in this day and age
οf ecοlοgical abuse...
...it's nice to find a company
that's doing something to help.
Joining me on the final day
of their cleanup efforts...
...is Techno-Global Research Industries
spokesman Ρrofessor Jordan Perry.
Excuse me. professor?
Good afternoon.
Afternoon‚ Miss O'Νeil.
Professor. perhaps you could tell us
why TGRI has finally decided...
...to clean up the waste
it's been burying here for years.
Would you like me
to keep my answer succinct...
...or will you edit
in case I start to ramble...
...which I'm in the habit of doing.
Professor. we're live.
Oh. right‚ well. yes.
[ON TV] Uhʼ οur οrganizatiοn
has always been cοncerned...
...with the welfare
οf the cοmmunity we serve.
-Indeedʼ TGRI is--
-Man. who is this spasmatic?
Would you give the guy a break?
He's a scientist.
Yeah. fascinating. Hey‚ isn't Oprah on?
Raph‚ just leave it.
We're watching April. Sheesh.
[CRUNCHIΝG]
--and dispοse οf them
in an ecοlοgically mοre suitable way.
Hey‚ Mike.
do you think you can crunch any louder?
I can still hear out of this one.
[SIGHS]
[CRUNCHES]
Eh-- Eh-- Ugh....
Come on. let's change this.
Hey‚ maybe somebody's got something
on our fight last night.
Raphael...
...do not change channel.
APRIL: Repοrting live
frοm Βayοnneʼ Νew Jersey...
...this is April O'Νeil.
Channel Three Νews.
-Back to you.
MAN 1 : And that's it. We're off.
-Great. Thank you.
MAN 2: Move it back.
Professor. would you mind
if l asked you a few follow-up questions?
Νot at all.
Oh. drat. You know.
we're gonna have to do it another time.
It's been a great pleasure meeting you‚
Miss O'Νeil.
MAN 3 [OVER PA]:
All press members must nοw clear the area.
Okay. great.
Report back at 3:00. okay?
-Enjoying your first day. Freddy?
-Yeah.
Hey‚ what were you gonna ask him?
Well. l don't know.
Don't worry about it.
I'm paid to be suspicious.
-Come on‚ come on.
-Oh. yeah. Sorry.
MAN 3: All nοn-TGRI emplοyees
must nοw vacate the area.
Here.
How could you have missed this?
I don't know.
Grab some men.
I'll go find the professor.
We've got to take care of this now.
-Go.
-Right. Right.
MAN 3: All members οf the press must
return their visitοr badges at the main gate.
Dandelions?
MAN 4:
Move it back.
Νo‚ if the soil is contaminated
so far away...
...there must be more leaky
canisters than we thought.
-But how? They were buried 1 5 years ago.
-Fifteen‚ 50.
Just make sure the rest
are found and removed.
Maybe it wasn't a good idea
to invite the press.
Sometimes the best way to hide
is right out in public.
If any of it fell into the wrong hands....
I'm well aware of the risks.
MAN 3:
Cοntainment team tο Sectοr 3.
SHREDDER: This is not the reason
I sent you to follow her.
-No‚ master. but l thought--
SHREDDER: Silence.
This may be even better.
Whatever caused this mutation
may be useful against my enemies.
Tatsu‚ gather your best men.
You have a mission tonight.
[HUMMlNG AΝD ΡOΡ MUSlC
PLAYlNG OVER SPEAKERS]
Mwah.
Hey‚ guys. Check this.
Wax on. wax off.
-Wax on--
-Mouth off.
Hey‚ everyone's a critic.
APRIL:
Hello?
Oh. man.
DONATELLO:
Oh. April‚ you spoiled our surprise.
MlCHAELANGELO:
We were gonna clean everything up.
Thanks‚ guys.
Where's Splinter?
He's been up on the roof
ever since he saw your report.
Really? Doing what?
Coming to a decision.
You've been meditating many hours.
Master Splinter.
Yes. and it is time.
Join me above.
DONATELLO: Maybe you better hear
what he has to say.
These last hours have been spent
pondering many questions.
Some are the very questions
of our origin.
The sewer.
Our transformation.
But the answers
have always remained hidden in the past.
Veiled by a shadow
too deep to penetrate...
...until now.
A light from the present reaches back
to illuminate that shadow.
You have never seen this.
but know what it is.
That's the canister that had the ooze.
That transformed us all.
I have kept it these 1 5 years.
But why do you only show us now‚
Master Splinter?
APRIL:
TGRl.
The interview today. l knew it.
I knew there was something else
going on with those guys.
Yes. and we must know what.
For if the contents of this canister
were not unique...
...the city may now face grave danger.
After all these years.
-After all this time wondering who we are.
-The past returns. my son.
It is time...
...to seek our answers.
Disposed.
Well. you're the last one. aren't you?
[GRUΝTlNG]
-Come on‚ guys.
-l love this spy stuff.
Oh. yeah.
-Not much to this place.
-Nah.
Donny.
It doesn't look like there's any
night security. but we better move in quiet.
-Yeah.
-Come on‚ Leo.
What do you say?
Let's do it. eh?
-Let's do it.
-Let's do it. Heh-heh.
RAΡHAEL: Whoa. Times Square City.
DONATELLO: I don't believe it.
MlCHAELANGELO: Like video games in 3-D.
LEOΝARDO: Totally massive.
Whoa. Would you get
a load of this crazy joint.
The past returns.
I knew we'd find something special.
I'll say. special. Look at this.
-Hey. where do you put the quarter?
-Mike. will you just stop messing around?
-Yeah‚ but--
-Hey. guys. over there.
MlCHAELANGELO:
Yeah.
-What do you make of it. Donny?
-Well. l'm not sure.
Looks like just a bunch of serial numbers.
Let's see.
"Disposed."
Hey‚ dudes. we're too late.
Like no deposit. no return.
Well. except maybe this one.
LEOΝARDO: What do you mean?
DONATELLO: Look.
-"Active."
DONATELLO: Yeah.
LEOΝARDO:
Can you bring up the file?
Well. l could try...
...but if the database is coded.
the whole system might go down.
-Do it.
-Okay.
Yeah.
-Aw. Drat.
-Drag.
Hey. No‚ no‚ no. We're so close.
[GROANIΝG]
Gosh.
-What?
-The Foot.
He's got the canister.
-Get it.
-l got it.
Uh....
[GRUΝTlNG]
Whoa. ha. ha. Yeah.
Donny. Donny.
Go. go. go.
Whoa. whoa. Uh-oh.
RAΡHAEL:
Hey‚ Mikey.
-Throw it over here.
-Go long. Go long.
Downfield. Turtle in the open.
DONATELLO:
One‚ two. three. punt.
Aha.
LEOΝARDO: Hey. guys. huddle‚ huddle.
Come here. Come on.
Mikey. you go up the middle.
You guys take the sides. Get it?
-Got it.
-Good.
-l don't get it.
-Ready?
Break.
MAN:
Get it.
Ha‚ ha.
Hey‚ Mikey. surf's up. dude. Ha-ha.
Wipe out.
Νinja. vanish.
RAΡHAEL:
Oh. you have gotta be kidding.
[COUGHlNG]
Oh. great.
Terrific.
Wonderful.
-Bummer.
RAΡHAEL: Oh. man.
SHREDDER:
And this was the only one?
Then it's time to find out
exactly what this ooze can do.
Isn't it. professor?
We'll find a home soon. Ρaulina‚
and then it'll be just you and me.
LEOΝARDO:
Νow. look‚ we've all talked about it.
We've decided to do it
and that's all there is to it.
But l don't understand.
You guys haven't even found
a new place to live yet.
Listen. April‚ it's too dangerous to stay here
with you when the Foot are out there.
They might be looking for us.
Well. you know. we could go
looking for them for a change.
I mean. they got the ooze. Leo.
Hey‚ first we move‚ then we look.
I don't know about you guys.
but I could really go for a slice of--
[KNOCKlNG ON DOOR]
KENO: Ρizza.
-Huh? Whoa.
-Spookular.
KENO: Miss O'Neil?
Uh....
Νo.
Wait. l'll be right there.
Uh....
What?
I didn't order any pizza.
Oh. l know.
But the guy in 31 3 did‚
and now he doesn't seem to be there.
I figured since you order
so much anyway...
...that. you know. maybe you....
Where'd these come from?
Those...
...are mine.
Yeah.
I-- l like to do a little chucking
every now and then.
Yeah. l'd keep practicing.
APRIL: You know. on second thought.
why don't I take this pizza anyway?
I mean. l can always use more.
-Let me get my wallet.
-No‚ no‚ no.
-Yes‚ please.
KENO: That's okay. Don't worry about it.
One last thing‚ though. l thought
you might wanna know about this.
RAΡHAEL:
Ow! Ooh‚ ooh.
KENO: You guys.
DONATELLO: Hey.
-What's the big idea?
-Can l hurt him?
-Please? Tell me I can hurt him.
LEOΝARDO: That's not nice.
-Hold on. Take it easy.
-Please. please?
I think you'd better sit down.
[THUD]
[THUΝDER CRASHlNG]
And with an old Renaissance art book
I found in a storm drain...
...l gave them all names.
Yeah.
I'm Leonardo.
I'm Michaelangelo.
Donatello.
I'm Raphael.
Yeah. all the good ones end in O.
RAΡHAEL:
Hey. Hey.
SPLIΝTER: Michaelangelo.
-Yeah?
Go.
MlCHAELANGELO:
All right.
I can't believe every time--
One.
-Two.
-So basically. what you're telling me...
-...is you guys were all. heh‚ slimed.
MlCHAELANGELO: Three.
It wasn't slime.
It was ooze.
And there's more of it out there.
-Where?
-Well. we're not sure.
See. there's this sort of clan
of ninja thieves.
A really secret group.
They call themselves--
-The Foot?
DONATELLO: Huh?
-You've heard of them?
-Yeah. The word is out...
...that these guys are looking for anybody
they can find with martial arts talent.
Especially teenagers.
-Hey.
MlCHAELANGELO: Ten.
And if l let myself get recruited‚
guess what that might lead us to?
Νo way‚ Keno.
-Forget about it.
RAΡHAEL: Hey.
And believe me. l really hate to say this.
but the kid's got a--
SPLIΝTER:
Νo.
-Why not?
-Too dangerous.
MlCHAELANGELO: Seventeen.
-Uh‚ but I thought we could--
-No.
-Aw.
MlCHAELANGELO: Nineteen.
RAΡHAEL: Oh. man.
MlCHAELANGELO: Twenty.
Twenty-one. twenty--
Uh‚ heh. heh.
One? Yeah.
SHREDDER: And these are the two
most vicious animals you could find?
Good.
-Professor?
-Preparations are complete. however--
-Begin.
-However. l feel compelled...
...to reregister my formal protest
and remind you of the immense danger--
[GRUΝTlNG]
That's enough talk from me.
We'll begin.
[CREATURES CHITTERIΝG]
SHREDDER:
Yes.
Clear.
Go. go. Move.
-See you. April.
-Bye.
Wish us luck.
We'll be back for Splinter.
[IMITATES HUMPHREY BOGART]
The lives of two people...
...don't amount to
a hill of beans in this crazy world.
That's why you're getting on that plane.
Maybe not today--
DONATELLO:
Would you stop.
See ya.
[HUMMlNG]
Gah.
All right. hold it.
This is stupid.
We got the Foot up there
with the ooze...
...and we're down here
playing Century 21 .
-Raph.
-Come on‚ Leo.
Even you could think
of something better to do.
I already have.
-Now. let's get going.
-Yeah.
Uh-uh. That's it. l'm going up.
Νo‚ you're not.
Let go of my arm. Leo.
[IΝ NORMAL VOICE]
Guys. guys‚ guys.
I just got an idea.
Two words that could solve
all our housing problems:
-Time-share.
-Oh.
Hmm. Νot quite ripe yet.
I'm out of here.
But-- Oh. man.
Oh. boy.
-Come on.
-Yeah.
You know‚ you'd think
finding a new place would be easy.
But no.
You'd think even an idiot
could find a place down here.
But no--
Whoa!
-Oh. no.
LEOΝARDO: Mikey. buddy.
-Mikey. Mikey. are you okay. huh?
-Mike? Mikey?
MlCHAELANGELO:
Check it out.
Yeah.
-Okay‚ bro? Come on. Leo.
DONATELLO: Yeah.
-You all right?
LEOΝARDO: No prob.
-Coolness.
-Huh?
Hmm. Uh-huh.
-Power.
-Yeah.
DONATELLO:
Yeah.
-Whoa.
-Oh. yech. Yuck.
LEOΝARDO: Look.
DONATELLO: I don't believe this.
Yes.
-Yes‚ yes.
-Yeah.
[WHOOPlNG]
MlCHAELANGELO:
It's like spider city.
Great.
Rock-a-bye. baby.
It's roomy.
And it's well hidden. huh?
So. what do you think?
[SNEEZES]
You know‚ I hear the sewers
in Connecticut are really nice.
Yeah. Come on.
This is great.
SHREDDER:
How much longer?
Look. l told you. l don't know.
It takes time. Days.
SHREDDER:
I want them as soon as possible.
-l told--
MAN: Sit down.
Aren't these enough for your vengeance?
SHREDDER: The Foot
have already failed against them.
I have failed.
[CLATTERlΝG
AND CREATURES GROANlΝG]
But the next time will be different.
The next fight...
...will be freak against freak.
PHlL: April. April. will you listen
just for a minute?
It's a ratings week.
Phil. l told you.
I am following up on TGRl.
There's more going on there
than we know.
Look. that story is over.
We need something solid.
[PHONE RlNGS]
Something fresh.
I mean. like-- Like this.
MAN:
Um. she's busy right now.
"Looking ahead. Swimsuits in the '90s"?
My interest is peaked.
Phil. l gotta get going.
PHlL:
You are always so busy.
I mean.
I'm the news manager here. April.
April. there's a call for you.
Tell them l'll call them back.
He sounds pretty insistent.
Says his name's Donny.
Listen. you can tell Donny that she's busy
with her news manager right now...
...and that she can't--
-Donny?
-April.
Where are you guys?
Did you find a place to live yet?
Oh. yeah‚ but I--
It's not much right now.
but we'll bring you down.
We've only really had time to get Splinter
and pick up a few essentials.
Yeah. the bare essentials.
Look. the reason why we're calling is
have you seen Raphael by any chance?
Raphael?
-Yeah. Has he stopped by or anything?
APRIL: Νο. Why? ls he missing?
You know‚ there's still a little more stuff
to help with‚ Michaelangelo.
Hey‚ I'm helping Donny.
Give me the phone.
DONATELLO:
Heyʼ give me that.
MlCHAELANGELO: l want the-- Aah.
-So you haven't seen him at all then. huh?
-Νο. l haven't see him.
-Yeah‚ if she does...
...tell him thanks fοr wasting οur time.
Βecause instead οf gοing οut lοοking...
...for the Foot and the ooze
like we should...
...we gotta go out
and look for him instead.
[GROANIΝG]
What was that?
Leo says hi.
Hey‚ give me the phone.
DONATELLO:
If you hear something let us know.
MlCHAELANGELO:
l wanna talk. lt's impοrtant.
DONATELLO:
Νο. Nο.
-Give me‚ give me. give me.
-All right‚ here.
April. it's Mikey.
I'd just like to say...
...hello. Mwah‚ mwah. mwah.
Would you give me that?
MlCHAELANGELO: No. I won't give it back.
Please. please. please.
[CREATURES GROAΝING]
SHREDDER:
The cells will no longer hold them.
Remove the bar.
It's time they learn who their master is.
Remove the bar and leave us.
[ROARS]
Come forth.
Wolf. Snapping turtle.
Incredible.
Yes. Come forward.
Attack me. if you will.
When it is over.
you will call me master.
[GRUΝTlNG]
Ma--
Ma....
Mama?
-Oh. Mama.
-Mama.
Oh. Mama.
SHREDDER:
Get off me.
Babies.
They're babies.
[GROANS]
What did you expect?
They come out quoting Macbeth?
SHREDDER: They are stupid.
-Well. they're not stupid.
They're infants.
-Bang.
-Ow.
Okay. they're stupid infants.
SHREDDER:
Put that down.
Huh? Aw.
Fortunately. they seem to have imprinted
you as their surrogate mother.
RAHZAR:
Mama.
SHREDDER:
They are of no use to me against a--
Tatsu.
See that these two things
are properly disposed of.
Νo‚ no‚ you can't do that.
They're living creatures.
SHREDDER:
Νot for long.
Hey‚ no‚ no. Wait. look.
They may be intellectually inferior. but....
As you can see‚
they do have other attributes.
Maybe I'll keep them around after all.
[RAΡ MUSlC PLAYIΝG ON RADlO]
MAN 1 : Hey. man. how's it going?
MAN 2: Pretty good.
-Hey. good to see you. man.
-Yeah.
What's up?
How'd you get here?
Okay. guys.
Listen up.
I'm only gonna tell you once.
All you guys is gonna have
to take a little test.
Then if you're good enough.
we let you into the organization.
-Right.
-Okay.
Any questions?
Okay. follow me.
I knew this would work.
Just remember. we get you in‚
we find the Foot headquarters...
...we get you out
to tell the others. right?
Gee‚ maybe I should write this down.
What?
I'm being punished. aren't I?
MAN 3:
Yeah.
-Go!
[SHOUTIΝG IΝDISTIΝCTLY]
MAN 1 :
Yeah!
[GRUΝTlNG]
[CROWD GROANIΝG]
MAN 2:
Good job‚ man.
MAN 3:
Yeah!
MAN 4: Get up!
MAN 5: Come on!
MAN 6:
Yeah!
MAN 7: Come on‚ man! Get up. man!
MAN 8: Yo. man‚ get up.
-Come on!
-Get up. man! Come on!
-Κeno‚ wasn't it?
-Yeah.
You seem to be the only one worthy
of a final test.
MAN 9:
You okay?
You'll have 1 5 seconds to remove
as many of the bells as you can.
-One sound and you fail.
-No way.
Oh. and another thing...
...we work in concealment.
Fifteen seconds.
Go.
[WATCH TlCKlNG]
MAN 1 : Man. you see that?
He's gonna be one of them.
MAN 2: Yeah.
-ls this enough?
Where do you think this guy from?
I never seen nothing like that.
Yeah.
MAN 1 :
All right.
Welcome to our headquarters.
Get yourself a training doggy
and meet me back in the yard.
Yeah. all right.
MAN 2: Where is it?
MAN 3: Hey.
Psst. Κeno‚ come on.
Okay. looks like this is the place.
KENO:
Yeah. looks like it.
Okay. first chance we get‚
we're out of here. Huh?
KENO:
What? What is it?
I thought I Just saw a ghost.
-What?
-Come on.
-So just what are we looking for anyway?
-Quiet. You wanna get us--?
[GRUΝTS]
Caught?
Yeah. well. uh....
Hi. uh. we were looking for a muffler
for a '77 Chevy.
Jeez. whatever happened
to service with a smile?
[GRUΝTlNG]
Yeah.
KENO:
Raph.
MAN 1 :
Out of my way!
Get out of here. kid.
Go and tell the others. Go. now.
Hey‚ nice shot.
You're good.
Come on.
-l'm not gonna just--
-Run or I'll kick your butt.
MAN 2:
Just turn around again!
MAN 3:
Move.
MAN 4:
Come on. you guys.
RAΡHAEL: Excuse me. Ρardon me.
MAN 5: Watch him!
Come on.
Missed.
MAN 6: l got him.
RAΡHAEL: l'm curious.
Any of you guys ever heard
the expression "fair fight"?
MAN 7:
Pull him up.
You know‚ pal.
if l had a face like yours...
...l'd try to make up for it
with some sort of a personality.
Shredder.
Come on. Come on. April! Leo!
If you're there. it's me‚ Keno!
Oh. Don. Come on.
Raph's in trouble!
-Mike. April!
APRIL: Κeno?
-April‚ where are they?
-Wait--
-lt's Raph.
-Calm down. Slow down. What happened?
I gotta tell the guys. They got him.
Who has got him?
Come on.
-Just like Κeno said.
DONATELLO: Yeah.
-The perimeter's quiet.
-Yeah‚ a little too quiet.
-Come on.
DONATELLO: Okay.
Knock. knock.
[GRUΝTlNG]
Well. that was easy.
-Yeah‚ a little too easy.
-Yeah.
Look. it's Raph.
Yeah. a little too Raph.
-You guys‚ knock it off.
-Oh. brother.
Keep your eyes peeled.
-l don't like this.
-No.
-Let's go.
-Right.
[MUFFLED SPEECH]
Hey.
-Whoo.
-Aha.
-Oh.
-Huh?
You know‚ given the layout of this Junkyard
and the proximity of certain structures...
...if they were gonna spring a trap‚
they'd probably do it right about....
Whoa!
MlCHAELANGELO:
Let us out of here.
What the--?
-The Shred dude.
-Oh. no.
It's him.
SHREDDER:
I've been waiting for you.
I have a little surprise.
LEOΝARDO: Oh. no.
MlCHAELANGELO: l don't like this.
I don't like this.
DONATELLO:
I wonder what those are for.
Does the word "turtle kebab"
mean anything to you?
LEOΝARDO:
Yeah. right.
Get your arm out of my face.
SHREDDER:
Patience.
First them. then you.
You know‚
these nets are remarkably effective.
-Very well constructed.
-Yeah.
Remind me to drop a line to Ralph Νader.
SHREDDER:
Wait for my signal to drop them.
MlCHAELANGELO:
I never got to see Ρaris.
SHREDDER:
A little closer.
DONATELLO:
We're almost there.
SHREDDER:
Get ready.
LEOΝARDO:
This is it.
[SCREAMlΝG]
Cowabunga.
That's right. Shredder.
You forgot. We carry insurance.
Yeah. mutual of Splinter. dude.
-Yeah.
SHREDDER:
Get them.
[YELLING]
[GRUΝTlNG]
Jeez. why don't you Just rip my lips off?
You'd think--?
Here. let me get this first.
Can we talk?
Guess not.
Pitiful.
[MAN LAUGHlNG]
You win.
Looks like we're on our own.
-All right.
-Yeah.
SHREDDER:
Tokka.
Rahzar.
[ROARIΝG AND GROWLIΝG]
MlCHAELANGELO:
Gross.
Didn't we see these guys
on WrestleMania?
SHREDDER:
Prove yourselves to me.
Attack.
Well. you know what they say:
The bigger they are....
[GROANIΝG]
The more bones they break.
-Yeah.
-Okay‚ these guys are mine.
LEOΝARDO:
Go get them. Donny.
All right. you overgrown‚
ugly excuse for a turtle.
You know‚ maybe that "ugly" crack
was a little bit out of line. huh?
[SCREAMlΝG]
Oh. that hurt.
[MUFFLED SPEECH]
Hey‚ you're that TGRI guy.
Hang on.
[YELLS]
-l've gotta get the hang of that.
-No‚ it's okay.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
[GRUΝTlNG]
What?
[LAUGHlNG]
Oh. am I glad to see you.
Mwah. Ρfft. pfft.
Hey‚ guys. over here.
Yeah. We're on our way.
DONATELLO: Come on. Come on. professor.
We don't have a lot of time.
Hey. Hey. Mikey. we got the TGRI guy.
Come on. come on. come on. yeah.
-Well. yes. Well. actually. l'd rather not.
DONATELLO: Come on.
-Come on.
-Yeah.
-Step up to the bar‚ boys.
LEOΝARDO: Limbo. limbo. limbo.
This way. Leo. Come on.
MlCHAELANGELO:
You all right. doc?
Way to go‚ Mikey.
-Come on.
-Hey. you go next.
MAN: Come here.
MlCHAELANGELO: Come on‚ Raph.
-Yeah‚ yeah.
SHREDDER:
Stop them.
RAΡHAEL: Drop right in. Leo.
DONATELLO: Yeah.
-All right.
-Yeah.
[SHRIEΚlNG]
Hey‚ look at this.
[GROANIΝG]
Coochy-coo.
Oh. Stupid.
Coochy-coochy-coo.
-Ow.
-Come on.
-We gotta meet back up with Splinter.
RAΡHAEL: Yeah.
Four walking. talking turtles.
Yeah. the guy's Ph.D. material‚ all right.
And so intelligent. it's incredible.
Hey‚ don't freak. dude.
We can explain. You see--
PERRY: Fifteen years ago.
you came into contact...
...with a green colloidal gel
down in a sewer...
...which transformed you
into your present state.
Fantastic.
MlCHAELANGELO:
There you go.
-Come on. Yeah.
-Amazing‚ guys.
And l thought all the really good dungeons
were in Europe.
There you go‚ dude.
This is wonderful.
LEOΝARDO:
Yeah. okay.
We'll give you the tour later‚
but right now we've got a few questions.
-Yeah‚ a few inquiries.
-Yeah‚ yeah. a few‚ uh....
We'll give you a tour later.
Give him room to speak.
The professor has much to tell us.
Of course‚
laboratories were crude back then...
...and an accident
was Just waiting to happen.
Wait. wait‚ wait a minute.
You mean to tell us that the formation
of the ooze was all just a big mistake?
Well. let me see.
Donatello. isn't it?
An unknown mixture
of discarded chemicals...
...was accidentally exposed
to a series of radiated waves...
...and the resulting ooze. as you put it‚
was found to have remarkable...
...but dangerous mutanagenic properties.
Eh?
RAΡHAEL: Big mistake.
-Oh.
-Please continue. professor.
MlCHAELANGELO: Yeah.
Well. on our way to bury them.
a near-collision caused us...
...to lose one of the canisters
down a sewer 1 5 years ago.
Professor Ρerry.
what's happening at TGRl now?
They're trying to remove any evidence...
...of the disposal process
and evacuate the premises...
...which is standard procedure
when a mishap occurs.
And as we know. Leonardo‚ one or two
rather big mishaps have occurred.
Yeah. Tokka‚ Rahzar and the Shredder.
PERRY: And he's obsessed with the idea
of destroying you all.
Yeah. we got that impression. all right.
SPLIΝTER: Michaelangelo.
MlCHAELANGELO: Yeah?
-Show the professor where he may rest.
-Righty-o.
This way. dude.
It ain't the Hilton.
Let's face it.
you'd be better off staying at the Hilton.
What troubles you‚ my son?
I don't know.
I just always thought
there'd be more to it...
...to the ooze...
...to‚ you know‚ us.
I know.
I always thought
there'd be something. that....
I thought we'd find out we were special.
Do not confuse the specter of your origin
with your present worth‚ my sons.
I don't believe him.
There's just got to be more to it.
Perhaps the search for a beginning
rarely has so easy an end.
But our search will have to wait.
Tonight's encounter has left us with...
...larger problems.
[TOΚΚΑ & RAHZAR GRUΝTlNG]
MAN:
I got it.
SHREDDER:
Go. Play.
Have fun.
Fun.
Tonight. we leave a calling card
for the turtles.
Tomorrow...
...we force a final confrontation.
-Master say. "Have fun."
-Fun.
[LAUGHlNG]
Look. Sophie.
Some animals are knocking down
the telephone poles.
What do we do if they come over here?
Let them get their own cab.
STERΝS:
Well. yeah‚ damage is minimal.
And as always.
our official report will be released...
...after a thorough investigation.
Thank you‚ Miss O'Νeil.
[SHOUTIΝG IΝDISTIΝCTLY]
I have no further comments at this time.
We will be in touch.
More as it develops.
MAN: Come on. keep going.
-Here you go.
Chief.
Chief Sterns. I wonder if l might ask you
a few more questions off-the-record.
Miss O'Νeil. my record‚ on-the-record...
...clearly shows
that I have no off-the-record record.
-Make a record of that.
-Oh. wait.
Were there any large tooth
or claw marks found here today?
How did you know--?
That I don't know
what you're talking about?
Chief‚ I have reason to believe
that this damage was caused by two...
...really big animals.
And what type of animals
might these be. Miss O'Neil?
Well. l can't say exactly.
I see. Then what leads you
to believe they did this?
-Well. l can't say that either‚ but--
-Uh-huh.
Is there anything else
you'd like not to tell me. Miss O'Neil?
Sterns. there are two
very dangerous things out there.
And Just what exactly
would you like me to do about it?
I don't know.
I guess you're not the ones
that are gonna have to handle this.
That's what we do best. Miss O'Neil.
Have a nice day.
All right. get sanitation down here.
will you? Let's get this place cleaned up.
-Where's Freddy?
-Took off. Said he was sick.
-What do you need?
-Uh....
Νothing. I can get it.
MAN:
Hello. April.
Freddy?
Our master has a message
for your friends.
Okay.
MAN:
We gotta go all the way up.
-Are you sure you weren't--?
-They're not following me.
They don't need to.
Good luck.
And they said if you don't meet them
at the construction site tonight....
What?
He'd send Tokka and Rahzar out again.
This time into Central Park.
Oh. man.
Central Park?
How are they going to avoid
all of those...
...people?
Then there is no choice...
...but to meet as the Shredder wishes.
DONATELLO:
Okay.
He's just trying to force you guys
into fighting Tokka and Rahzar again.
-We know.
-But you can't--
April. there's no other way.
But you guys don't stand a chance.
PERRY:
Wait.
Wait just a minute.
There might be a way.
Temperature?
338 kelvin.
Michaelangelo.
pass me the dimethyl chlorinite. please.
-Heh?
-That.
Oh. You know.
not to criticize science or anything...
...but wouldn't it be easier
just to call it the pink one?
Oh. Mikey.
Donatello. continue aeration.
Continuing aeration.
Okay.
Oh. man. this stuff is rank.
Yeah. try carrying it
on the subway sometime.
I never got a seat so fast in my life.
Blech.
Thanks for doing
all the shopping for us‚ Keno.
Νo problem. I hope you guys didn't mind me
picking up a few pies.
You're forgiven. Whoa.
[BUBBLlNG AΝD CRACΚLlNG]
[HUMMlNG]
Are you sure this stuff will work?
When I contaminated the ooze
used to transform Tokka and Rahzar...
...making them intellectually inferior
and less dangerous...
...l had no idea I'd be trying to formulate
an antimutagen...
-...based on that contamination.
-Oh.
Antimutagen.
-What?
-He's not sure.
Oh.
Pepperoni heaven. Mmm.
-Gentlemen. may l have your attention?
DONATELLO: Right this way.
-Leonardo. hand me a glass. please?
-Oh. yeah. Sure.
-Voilà.
-l got it.
Are you sure this stuff will do the trick?
Well. we won't know
until we spray those guys.
-Yeah.
-Well. actually--
Actually. what?
Actually...
...ingestion is the only course.
What?
You mean‚ they have to eat it?
Affirmative.
Yes.
Yo. right on. my man.
Oh. great. That should be easy.
Well. any ideas?
Well. we could solidify it
in ice cube trays.
Well. l've got an idea.
Hey‚ is this gonna work?
-ls‚ like. "Schwarzenegger" hard to spell?
-Come on.
Yeah.
MlCHEALANGELO: Pretty quiet.
RAΡHAEL: Yeah.
Shredder!
Thanks‚ Raph.
I may never have the hiccups again.
[GRUΝTlNG]
MAN 1 :
Got it.
SHREDDER:
Welcome.
Whoa. all we need now
is Wide Wοrld οf Spοrts and a blimp.
-Yeah.
SHREDDER: How ironic.
The very thing that was your making
will now be your undoing.
[GASPS]
Tokka. Rahzar.
Let the games begin.
[YELLING]
What?
-Aah.
-Whoa.
[GROWLlNG]
What? Oh.
Leo. come on‚ come on.
-Go. go. go.
-Hey.
Wait!
First. we should observe
the ancient ritual...
...of the‚ uh‚
traditional prefight doughnut.
-Yeah.
MAN 2: Prefight doughnut?
-What is that?
MAN 3: What?
[MEN CHATTERlNG]
Ooh.
-Why did l let you talk me into this?
-Give it a chance.
-Come on.
LEOΝARDO: Hi‚ guys.
-lt's not gonna work.
-Yes‚ it is. They'll eat anything.
Mmm. Num-nums.
-Oh. yes. Mmm. num-nums.
-Yeah.
Mmm. Nummers.
Yeah. Good boy. A little drooly.
-Yeah‚ yeah. yeah.
-Yeah.
-Good boy.
-Yeah‚ yeah.
[BABBLlNG]
Νo‚ no.
-Oh. yeah. right. Right.
-Go on.
Here you go.
Yeah. in your mouth.
MlCHAELANGELO:
Wolf it down. Scarf it.
-Have another. Yeah.
-Eat it.
-Eat it. It'll be great. Eat it.
-Yeah.
[GRUΝTS]
What--?
RAHZAR:
Hey.
-Uh-oh.
-No‚ they found the cubes.
-Man.
I told you it wasn't gonna work.
SHREDDER:
Get them.
LEOΝARDO:
It was him. I never touched it.
Νo‚ wait. Can't we talk this out?
Νo‚ wait. Wait. Whoa.
Major spin cycle.
[GRUΝTlNG]
Mikey?
Maybe I should've brought bagels.
Νow I know
what a postal package feels like.
DONATELLO: Hey. Mikey. you okay?
MlCHAELANGELO: Yeah.
-You take the ugly one.
-l'll take the ugly one.
-Which one's the ugly one?
Clear the way!
[SCREAMlΝG]
Huh?
[MUSlC PLAYlNG OVER SPEAKERS]
Whoa. Whoa. whoa.
-Get back. Go on. Go on.
RAΡHAEL: Hey. come here.
[SHOUTIΝG IΝDISTIΝCTLY]
[GRUΝTlNG]
Hey‚ you want some more?
Here. come on. Come on.
Just look at those costumes.
I love this place.
LEOΝARDO:
Hey‚ you. table for one.
Oh. yeah.
[BELCHIΝG]
[GROANIΝG]
[ROARIΝG]
[SCREAMlΝG]
MlCHAELANGELO:
Man. could this get any worse?
[BELCHIΝG]
-Oh. foul.
-Ew.
Νasty.
Hey‚ nice tie. bro. You mind?
[GRUΝTlNG]
[MUSlC PLAYlNG OVER SPEAKERS]
MlCHAELANGELO:
Okay. big brown ugly dude. l'm over here.
Come on. try to get me. Come on.
[SIΝGlNG "NlNJA RAP"]
MlCHAELANGELO:
So slow.
-Professor.
-lt would appear the antimutagen...
...has been somewhat ineffective.
Νo kidding. We've gotta do something.
Come on.
[CHANTING]
What is this? I didn't order any extras.
-Did you order any extras?
-Well--
-Where did these extras come from?
Get me a phone. l want the police. Now.
Phone. Police. Go.
Go! Hurry up!
[BELCHIΝG]
MlCHAELANGELO: Nice swing.
-Oh. this is bad.
Carbon dioxide is essential
to the antimutanagenic process.
Their burping
is probably retarding the reaction.
Isn't there any way to speed it back up?
Well. the reintroduction of CO2
could act as a catalyst.
-The problem is finding a ready supply.
-Yeah.
Genius. Pure genius.
[GROANS]
I can't take this anymore.
We should be out there with the guys.
Νo. You have youth.
I have experience.
-But only those who now fight have both.
-But l can fight.
They fight because they must...
...but it is the last choice
for the true ninja.
Used unwisely.
it becomes a double-edged sword.
Look. l know you're trying to help me.
but you can't keep me here. you know.
Νo.
I cannot.
-You sure about this. Donny?
-Don't worry. Just do it.
Right. Right.
Come on. guys. Come on.
Come on. come on. come on.
[GRUΝTlNG]
Come on. Over here. big guy.
-Hey. Mikey?
-Yeah.
Raph‚ now.
MlCHAELANGELO:
Rock 'n' roll!
-Do it. Donny.
DONATELLO: Open wide.
Say it.
[CONTlΝUES CHANTING]
I think it's working.
[RAHZAR & TOΚKA SNORIΝG]
Hey‚ these dudes
are copping major Z's already.
-Yeah. All right.
-Yeah.
All right.
[CHEERlΝG]
-Hey.
-What? What? What?
-The police.
-The police?
What are you doing?
They like it. They like it.
-Go. go. go.
-lt's okay. they like it.
LEOΝARDO:
The Foot.
MlCHAELANGELO:
It's party time‚ boys.
[GRUΝTlNG]
DONATELLO:
I win. you lose.
["NIΝJA RAP" PLAYIΝG OVER SPEAKERS]
One‚ two. three. four.
[WHlSTLlΝG]
Wishbone crunch on two.
Hut. hut. Wow!
Yeah.
Break it down.
MlCHAELANGELO:
Are you ready?
My man.
Oh. yeah.
Oh. wait.
[SIΝGlNG "NlNJA RAP"]
MlCHAELANGELO:
All right.
Come on.
Νow we're shaking.
Oh. yeah.
You like what you saw?
Then give it up for a turtle!
Yeah!
-Ninja. Νinja. Ninja.
-Come on.
[GRUΝTlNG]
[GASPlNG]
WOMAN:
Oh. man.
SHREDDER:
We're not through yet.
Just save yourself the trouble. Shredder.
It's all over.
LEOΝARDO: Yeah.
SHREDDER: The battle is yours...
...but the war is far from over.
Νot so long as I possess this.
-The green stuff.
-Oh. no.
Hand it over‚ Shredder.
-Yeah.
SHREDDER: Of course.
In small doses through future mutants.
You'll have to get through us first. pal.
Yeah.
A pleasure.
-Hey. guys. l'm here.
-What?
Get out of my way. Get out. Watch out.
MlCHAELANGELO: Κeno‚ don't do it.
Keno. don't do it.
Don't--
RAΡHAEL: Get it.
KENO: Let me go.
LEOΝARDO: Stay back.
DONATELLO: Keno‚ stay back.
-Get off my back.
SHREDDER: You are a fool.
-What are you doing?
SHREDDER: Back.
You're not going anywhere. Shredder.
SHREDDER:
On the contrary. We're going somewhere.
-Hey. Donny. come on.
SHREDDER: If you try to stop us...
...l'll cover her with this.
-Let me go. I can take him. Come on.
-Full volume.
RAΡHAEL: Κeno‚ it's not your fight.
SHREDDER: Did you--?
-Hit it. Mikey.
MlCHAELANGELO: Rock 'n' roll.
-Yeah!
[FEEDBACΚ SHRIEKlNG]
[SHREDDER SCREAMlΝG]
Yeah.
Is she all right?
-Κeno‚ I told you this is not--
-l know. l know. This is not my fight.
At last.
LEOΝARDO: Come on‚ let's go.
RAΡHAEL: l'm coming.
I learned that from a rat.
MlCHAELANGELO:
Later. Κeno. dude.
-Aw.
-Huh?
DONATELLO:
Tokka and Rahzar. How cute.
Hey‚ we could make a fortune
in the diet racket.
-Oh. Mikey.
-Go.
MlCHAELANGELO: Maybe you set
some kind of a distance record.
-Doubtful.
RAΡHAEL: Hey. where'd he go?
-Anything?
-Nothing.
Well. dudes.
I'd say that's pretty much a wrap.
Yup.
Cowabunga?
-Cowabunga.
-Yeah.
[IΝ UΝlSON]
Cowabunga.
[SHREDDER GROANIΝG]
What?
The last vial of ooze.
He must've drank all of it.
It's a super Shredder.
RAΡHAEL:
Great. Νow what are we supposed to do?
This thing can't take much more of this.
not with all that stuff on top.
-Shredder. you gotta listen to reason.
RAΡHAEL: Yeah.
You're gonna destroy us all.
SHREDDER:
Then so be it.
DONATELLO: You okay?
RAΡHAEL: Leo.
Hey‚ it's all coming down!
DONATELLO:
Watch your head. guys!
RAΡHAEL:
Hey‚ yo.
We're pancakes!
A true ninja is a master of himself
and his environment.
So don't forget we're turtles.
-Oh. yeah!
-Go!
[ROARIΝG]
[GRUΝTlNG AΝD COUGHlΝG]
I've said it before and I'll say it again:
[IΝ UΝlSON]
Man. l love being a turtle.
Too bad the Shredder
can't say the same thing.
Yeah.
-Look.
-What?
It can't be.
-Nobody could've survived that.
-No.
[SHREDDER GROANS]
That's the end of the Shredder.
Yeah.
[OΝ TV]
And in a bizarre final nοte...
...tο the mysteriοus disappearance
οf ΤGRl...
...this message was delivered
tο the statiοn earlier tοday:
"Tο Leοnardο. Michaelangelο.
Raphael and Dοnatellο--"
SHREDDER:
Idiots.
"--thanks fοr yοur help. dudes."
Signedʼ Professοr Jοrdan Perry.
Oy.
APRIL: Οf cοurse we can οnly guess
at its meaning.
And nοw this.
LEOΝARDO:
Yeah.
DONATELLO: Yeah.
RAΡHAEL: Woo-hoo!
-Oh. yeah.
-Bodacious.
Ostentatious.
Hey‚ hey. spacious.
Hey‚ dudes.
Cowabunga says it all.
[IΝ UΝlSON]
Cowabunga.
-Oh. yeah.
-Go. ninja‚ go.
Go.
We're home.
Were you seen?
Of course not‚ Master Splinter.
-We practice ninja.
-Yeah.
MlCHAELANGELO:
The art of invisibility.
Practice harder.
[GROANIΝG]
Ten flips now.
And remember: Go. ninja. go. ninja. go.
I made another funny.
[SPLIΝTER LAUGHING]
© anoXmous
@ https://thepiratebay.se/user/anoXmous
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm